[Music]
the snow glows white on the mountain
tonight not a footprint to be
seen A kingdom of
isolation and it looks like I'm the
queen the wind is howling like this
swirling storm
[Music]
inside Couldn't keep it and heav knows
I don't let them in don't let them see
be the good girl you always have to be
concealed don't feel don't let them
know well now they know
let it go let it go can't hold it back
anymore let it go let it go turn away
and slam my
door my don't care what they're going to
say let the storm rage
on never bed me anyway
it's funny how some
distance makes everything seem
small and the fears it once controlled
me can't get to me at
all it's time to see what I can do to
test the limits and break through no
right no wrong no rules for
me I'm free
Let it go Let it go I am one with the
wind and sky let it go let it go you'll
never see me
cry here I
stand Here I Stand let the sword rage on
[Music]
a power floures through the air into to
the
ground we saw this spiraling in frozen
fractal all
around and one thought
crystalizes like an
ny I'm never going back the past is in
the
he let it go let it go when I rise like
break
our let it go let it go let perfect girl
is
gone here I
stand in my light
of let a SW of r
the coal never bothered me anyway